A Guide to the Vincent P. Dole papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Correspondence, Series 1 FA730
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1960-1995; 1; 21.2 Box(es)
  - Marion, Ira J., 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - Marin, William R., 1964-1976 (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - Martinez, Julio, 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Maryland M.M.T.P., 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 279)
  - Maryland M.M.T.P. (Box 27, Folder 279A)
  - Maslansky, Robert A., 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 280)
  - Maslansky, Robert A. (Box 27, Folder 280A)
  - Mathsoft, Inc., 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 281)
  - Maurer, Herrymon, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 282)
  - Mauro, Alexander, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 283)
  - Mayor's Study Program, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 284)
  - McCarty, Maclyn, 1965-1990 (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - McConnell, Mary Jo (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - McDermott, Walsh, 1970-1980 (Box 27, Folder 287)
  - McEwen, Bruce S., 1995 (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - McLaughlin, Mary C., 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - McLellan, Andrew, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 290)
  - McMaster, Philip R.B., 1955-1987 (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Medicaid, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Medical Letter, 1968-1997 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Merck, Sharp, and Dohme, 1960-1986 (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - Methadone Magazine, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Methadone Programs, 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - Methadone Regulation, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 297)
  - Meyer, Roger E., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 298)
  - Michigan, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 299)
  - Millbank, Tweed, Hadley, and McCloy, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 300)
  - Miller, Sharon D. (Box 28, Folder 301)
  - Millman, Robert B., 1970-1992 (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Miras, Constantine, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - Misra, Anand L., 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - Modern Medicine, 1953-1975 (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - Mono Lake, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - Mora Narcotic Rehabilitation Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - Morris, Anne G., 1968-1977 (Box 28, Folder 308)
  - Mosteller, Frederick, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - Mount Sinai, 1967-1987 (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Mulé, Salvatore J., 1964-1983 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Mumford, Robert S., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Murtagh, John H., 1963-1968 (Box 29, Folder 314)
  - Murthy, S. Krishna, 1965-1989 (Box 29, Folder 315)
  - N Misc, 1968- 1983 (Box 29, Folder 316)
  - N Misc (Box 29, Folder 316A)
  - Narcotic and Drug Research, Inc., 1985-1991 (Box 29, Folder 317)
  - Nash, George, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 318)
  - National Drug and Alcohol Research Center, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 319)
  - National Institute of Mental Health, 1972-1989 (Box 29, Folder 320)
  - National News Council, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - Nature Conservancy, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Navy Department, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 323)
  - NDA International, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - New England Journal of Medicine, 1979-1990 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - New Jersey, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - Newman, Robert G. (1 of 11), 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 327)
  - Newman, Robert G. (2 of 11), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 328)
  - Newman, Robert G. (3 of 11), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 329)
  - Newman, Robert G. (4 of 11), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 330)
  - Newman, Robert G. (5 of 11), 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - Newman, Robert G. (6 of 11), 1984-1988 (Box 32, Folder 332)
  - Newman, Robert G. (7 of 11), 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 333)
  - Newman, Robert G. (8 of 11), 1981-1983 (Box 33, Folder 334)
  - Newman, Robert G. (9 of 11), 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 335)
  - Newman, Robert G. (10 of 11), 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 336)
  - Newman, Robert G. (11 of 11), 1970-1978 (Box 34, Folder 337)
  - Newman, Robert G. (Box 34, Folder 337A)
  - Newman, Robert G. Nominations, 1986-1994 (Box 34, Folder 338)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1981-1994 (Box 34, Folder 339)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 34, Folder 339A)
  - New York State Journal of Medicine, 1971-1978 (Box 34, Folder 340)
  - New York State Public Health Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 341)
  - New York Times, 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 342)
  - New York University Medical Center, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 343)
  - Nichols, Rodney W., 1978-1992 (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - Nightingale, Stuart L., 1971-1995 (Box 35, Folder 345)
  - Northeast Regional Methadone Treatment Coalition, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 346)
  - Nottebohm, Fernando, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 347)
  - O Misc, 1966-1975 (Box 35, Folder 348)
  - O Misc. (Box 35, Folder 348A)
  - Office of Technology Assessment, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 349)
  - Ohio M.M.T.P., 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 350)
  - Ollo, Christine L., 1973-1992 (Box 35, Folder 351)
  - Opiate Addiction Treatment Services, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 352)
  - Oregon M.M.T.P., 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 353)
  - Orraca, John, 1967-1992 (Box 36, Folder 354)
  - Orraca, John (Box 36, Folder 354A)
  - P Misc (1 of 2), 1969-1991 (Box 36, Folder 355)
  - P Misc (2 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 36, Folder 356)
  - P Misc (Box 36, Folder 356A)
  - P.A.C.T./N.A.D.A.P., 1972-1976 (Box 36, Folder 357)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 358)
  - Pais, Abraham, 1983-1991 (Box 36, Folder 359)
  - Palette, 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 360)
  - Palette (Box 36, Folder 360A)
  - Panda, Nimai C., 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 361)
  - Paoletti, Rodolfo, 1972-1978 (Box 37, Folder 362)
  - Parrino, Mark W., 1987-1991 (Box 37, Folder 363)
  - Parrino, Mark W. (Box 37, Folder 363A)
  - Participants in the Conference on Receptors and Human Disease, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 364)
  - Patterson, David, 1974-1977 (Box 37, Folder 365)
  - Patterson, David (Box 37, Folder 365A)
  - Pearman, Carmen (Box 37, Folder 366)
  - Peltz, Lawrence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 367)
  - Pendegar, Gerald, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 368)
  - Pendegar, Gerald (Box 37, Folder 368A)
  - Pennsylvania, 1966-1972 (Box 37, Folder 369)
  - Pert, Candace B., 1974-1983 (Box 37, Folder 370)
  - Pert, Candace B. (Box 37, Folder 370A)
  - Pfaffmann, Carl, 1987-1994 (Box 37, Folder 371)
  - Phencyclidine, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 372)
  - Phillipson, Richard, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 373)
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 374)
  - Plum, Fred, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 375)
  - Pope, Vernon, 1983-1988 (Box 37, Folder 376)
  - Pope, Vernon (Box 37, Folder 376A)
  - Project Cork (Box 37, Folder 377)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 378)
  - Public Health Research Institute of the City of New York, 1968-1979 (Box 38, Folder 379)
  - Public Relations, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 380)
  - Public Studies Corporation, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 381)
  - Puerto Rico, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 382)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 38, Folder 382A)
  - Q Misc, 1970-1974 (Box 38, Folder 383)
  - R Misc (1 of 3), 1969-1986 (Box 38, Folder 384)
  - R Misc (2 of 3), 1967-1988 (Box 38, Folder 385)
  - R Misc (3 of 3), 1970-1989 (Box 38, Folder 386)
  - R Misc (Box 38, Folder 386A)
  - Radioactive Materials License, 1965-1972 (Box 39, Folder 387)
  - Rasmussen, Christian, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 388)
  - Raventós, Rosa E. (Box 39, Folder 389)
  - Reeve Angel, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 390)
  - Reisinger, Marc, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 391)
  - Resnick, Richard, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 392)
  - Rezai, Abbas (Box 39, Folder 393)
  - Rhode Island M.M.T.P., 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 394)
  - Rhode Island M.M.T.P. (Box 39, Folder 394A)
  - Richter, Curt P., 1979-1985 (Box 39, Folder 395)
  - Rizack, Martin A., 1976 (Box 39, Folder 396)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1976-1986 (Box 39, Folder 397)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1977-1996 (Box 39, Folder 398)
    Material is closed from scholarly research.
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1950-1972 (Box 39, Folder 399)
  - Rockefeller Institute Library Committee, 1958-1964 (Box 39, Folder 400)
  - Rockefeller University Hospital Ethics Committee, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 401)
  - Rogers, David E., 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 402)
  - Roland, Ronald, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 403)
  - Ross, David, 1967-1981 (Box 39, Folder 404)
  - Rubin, Emmanuel, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 405)
  - S Misc (1 of 3), 1964-1993 (Box 40, Folder 406)
  - S Misc (2 of 3), 1969-1983 (Box 40, Folder 407)
  - S Misc (3 of 3), 1968-1995 (Box 40, Folder 408)
  - S Misc (Box 40, Folder 408A)
  - Samuels, Howard J., 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 409)
  - Sassoon, Humphrey F., 1972-1976 (Box 40, Folder 410)
  - Saunders, Marguerite T., 1994 (Box 40, Folder 411)
  - Schneider, Howard A., 1967-1983 (Box 40, Folder 412)
  - Schwartz, Felice N., 1993 (Box 40, Folder 413)
  - Schwartz, Irving L. (1 of 2), 1966-1987 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Schwartz, Irving L. (2 of 2), 1951-1978 (Box 41, Folder 415)
  - Scientific American, 1959-1986 (Box 41, Folder 416)
  - Seitz, Frederick, 1968-1993 (Box 41, Folder 417)
  - Sells, Saul B., 1968-1978 (Box 41, Folder 418)
  - Senay, Edward C., 1973-1982 (Box 41, Folder 419)
  - Shashaty, Nancy, 1969-1975 (Box 41, Folder 420)
  - Sheps, Cecil G., 1968-1993 (Box 41, Folder 421)
  - Simon, Eric J., 1969-1979 (Box 41, Folder 422)
  - Singer, Burton, 1977-1988 (Box 42, Folder 423)
  - Singer, Herbert M., 1988-1997 (Box 42, Folder 424)
  - Smith, Cedric M., 1979 (Box 42, Folder 425)
  - Smithers, R. Brinkley, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 426)
  - Snyder, Solomon H., 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 427)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 428)
  - Solomon, George F., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 429)
  - Sorokey, Gary R., 1988 (Box 42, Folder 430)
  - Spinney, Laura, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 431)
  - Stanbury, John B., 1983-1995 (Box 42, Folder 432)
  - Stanley Nelson and Associates, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 433)
  - Stengaard-Pederson, Kristian, 1976-1985 (Box 42, Folder 434)
  - Stevens, Harold A., 1972 (Box 42, Folder 435)
  - Stimmel, Barry, 1970-1993 (Box 43, Folder 436)
  - Stouffer Prize, 1971-1974 (Box 43, Folder 437)
  - Strange, R. H., 1981 (Box 43, Folder 438)
  - Sudak, Howard S., 1991 (Box 43, Folder 439)
  - Sudakov, Konstantin V., 1988 (Box 43, Folder 440)
  - Surgeon General’s Workshop on Drunk Driving, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Sutton, Perry E., 1968-1977 (Box 43, Folder 442)
  - Sweeney, Brion, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 443)
  - T Misc, 1969-1989 (Box 43, Folder 444)
  - T Misc (Box 43, Folder 444A)
  - Tagliamonte, Alessandro, 1987-1995 (Box 43, Folder 445)
  - Telegdi, Valentine, 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 446)
  - Texas M.M.T.P., 1969-1972 (Box 43, Folder 447)
  - Thailand, 1995-1998 (Box 43, Folder 448)
    - Presentation on Opiate and Heroin Addiction, ca. 1996; 2001:075:001; Slides.; Slides
      These items have been separated from the body of the collection to facilitate stabilization, migration, and long-term preservation. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Thomas, Lewis, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 449)
  - Thorn, Niels A., 1952-1997 (Box 44, Folder 450)
  - Torrens, Paul R., 1970-1975 (Box 44, Folder 451)
  - Towns, Edolphus, 1970-1978 (Box 44, Folder 452)
  - Transit Authority (Box 44, Folder 453)
  - Treatment Improvement Exchange, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 454)
  - Trigg, Harold L., 1990 (Box 44, Folder 455)
  - Trussell, Ray E., 1966-1978 (Box 44, Folder 456)
  - U Misc, 1968-1993 (Box 44, Folder 457)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 458)
  - United States General Accounting Office, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 459)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 460)
  - V Misc, 1968-1991 (Box 44, Folder 461)
  - V Misc (Box 44, Folder 461A)
  - Van de Wijngaart, G.F., 1985 (Box 44, Folder 462)
  - Vanden Heuvel, William J., 1971-1981 (Box 44, Folder 463)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D., 1971-1992 (Box 44, Folder 464)
  - Van Valer, Robert L., 1979-1991 (Box 44, Folder 465)
  - Vera Institute of Justice, 1968-1978 (Box 45, Folder 466)
  - Vesell, Elliot S., 1969-1982 (Box 45, Folder 467)
    A variety of Vesell's articles
  - Veterans Administration, 1972-1979 (Box 45, Folder 468)
  - Virgin Islands, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 469)
  - Vitarine, 1968-1973 (Box 45, Folder 470)
  - Vona, Leo (Box 45, Folder 471)
  - W Misc (1 of 2), 1969-1993 (Box 45, Folder 472)
  - W Misc (2 of 2), 1968-1989 (Box 45, Folder 473)
  - W Misc (Box 45, Folder 473A)
  - Wallace, Rodrick, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 474)
  - Walldius, Goran, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 475)
  - Warner, Alan, 1967-1979 (Box 46, Folder 476)
  - Warner, Alan (Box 46, Folder 476A)
  - Washington M.M.T.P., 1970 (Box 46, Folder 477)
  - Washington, D.C. M.M.T.P., 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 478)
  - Way, E. Leong, 1966-1987 (Box 46, Folder 479)
  - Webb, Arthur Y., 1990 (Box 46, Folder 480)
  - Weight, Forrest F., 1982-1994 (Box 46, Folder 481)
    A variety of drafts and submitted versions of Weight's work
  - Weiss, Jay M., 1983 (Box 46, Folder 482)
    A variety of papers by Weiss
  - Werner, Mario, 1966-1993 (Box 46, Folder 483)
  - White, Abraham G., 1969-1976 (Box 46, Folder 484)
  - Wickler, Abraham, 1963-1978 (Box 46, Folder 485)
  - Wiesenfeld-Hallin, Zsuzsanna, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 486)
  - Wiley and Sons, Inc., 1951-1961 (Box 47, Folder 487)
  - Wilson, Jerry V., 1993 (Box 47, Folder 488)
  - Wogan, Irmgard Oldbert, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 489)
  - Wolf, John S., 1969-1978 (Box 47, Folder 490)
  - Wolkstein, Eileen, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Wolkstein, Eileen (Box 47, Folder 491A)
  - Wood-Cahusac, Sydney, 1981-1983 (Box 47, Folder 492)
  - Wyngaarden, James B., 1974-1989 (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Xavier University of Louisiana, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 494)
  - Y Misc, 1969-1989 (Box 47, Folder 495)
  - Z Misc, 1969-1990 (Box 47, Folder 496)
  - Zacny, James P., 1995 (Box 47, Folder 497)
  - Zaks, Arthur, 1972-1977 (Box 47, Folder 498)
  - Zavelttini, Emilio, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 499)
  - Zierler, Kenneth, 1986-1992 (Box 48, Folder 500)
  - Zimmerman, David R., 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 501)
  - Zinberg, Norman (1 of 2), 1978-1989 (Box 48, Folder 502)
  - Zinberg, Norman (2 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 503)
  - Zoll, Daniel (Box 48, Folder 504)
  - Zweben, Joan Ellen, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 505)
  - Zwerling, Charles, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 506)